<resources>
    <string name="app_name">အောင်ရဲဇော်</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello World!!!</string>
    <string name="btnOne">ONE</string>
    <string name="btnTwo">TWO</string>
    <string name="mlbb">Mobile Legends</string>
    <string name="aboutOeL">Oeschinensee (Oeschinin Lake) is one of the premier alpine lake destinations in Switzerland. The azure blue water is surrounded by towering ridges, which are covered in snow in the winter and melt into waterfalls into the summer. It’s truly a magical amphitheater, which was almost too beautiful to believe. In this blog post, I will share with you our hiking route, some tips on epic little viewpoints and all the details about how to get there, the best time of year to visit and all the good stuff you need to know before you visit Oeschininsee (Oeschinin Lake).

Hike Duration: 1 hour to Oeschinen Lake from Kandersteg (Additional for hiking around the lake)

Hike Distance: 4km

Hike Difficulty: Easy. Children on the trail. Short but steep. Hiking to the cabins is steeper but still safe.

Hike Incline: Starting point at Kandersteg: 1,174m – Oeschinensee height: 1,578m


HOW TO GET TO OESCHINENSEE (OESCHININ ALPINE LAKE)
To reach Oeschinensee from Zurich it will take about 2.5 hours on the train or 2 hours by car. You will need to arrive in the town of Kandersteg, which is also the name of the train station. From Kandersteg, the path is very well signed and leads you across a small bridge to the ticket office/cable car ticketing station. Here there is a big map, which is a great visual to help you decide which route to take. We decided to go rogue and hike in (not that hard) rather than take the cable car, which as of 2019 was $30 USD return or $22 USD one way. The hike to the lake took us fifty minutes so it really isn’t value for money if you are physically capable as it isn’t a scenic cable car (by Swiss standards).



Mediavine
I backpacked around Switzerland by using trains and buses. They are very efficient, have good coverage and are also very damn expensive. What I did is bought the Swiss Half-Fare Card, which gives you half price off any ticket (except some cable cars) It basically pays itself off within five days so if you are there for a week you NEED it. If you are looking to move across the country quickly and doing some big train journeys they will be more than $100 USD sometimes. Many people get the Swiss Travel Pass, which is pretty expensive about $100 USD a day but gives you unlimited free travel and half price on many cable cars. I’d say get the Swiss Half-Fare Pass for sure but don’t rush into the full Swiss Travel Pass until you have mapped out your route.  The other alternative if you are traveling all over Europe you should look into how to save money with the Eurail Pass, which could be an even better option than the Swiss-specific train passes. </string>
    <string name="payment_methods">Payment Methods</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="mission1">Duis tellus metus,elementum a lectus id, aliquet interdum mauris. Nam bibendum efficitur sollicitudin. Proin eleifend libero velit, nec fringilla dolor finibus
    quis. nMorbi eu libero pellentesque, rutrum metus quis blandit est. Fusce bibendum accumsan nisi vulputate feugiat. In fermentum laoreet euismod. Praesent sem nislm,
    facilisis eget odio at, rhoncus scelerisque ipsum. Nulla orci duim dugnissim a risus utm lobortis porttitor velit.</string>
    <string name="mission2">Nulla id lectus metus. Maecenas a lorem in odio auctor facilisis non vitae nunc. Sed malesuada volutpat massa. Praesent sit amet lacinia augue,</string>
</resources>